Prakriti Shaurya Senior System Engineer - Infosys Limited

Mangalore, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Prakriti-Shaurya/5339383f9294887e

Detail-oriented individual with three years of experience as an IT Consultant looking

for opportunity to develop my professional skills in a vibrant and stable environment,

and to use those skills for the benefits of the organization in best possible way.

Willing to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka - Bangalore Urban, Karnataka

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior System Engineer

Infosys Limited - Mangalore, Karnataka -

January 2017 to Present

Working as an IT Consultant under application maintenance and support for METLIFE Insurance company.

System Engineer

Infosys Limited - Mangalore, Karnataka -

December 2014 to December 2016

Worked as an IT Consultant under application maintenance and support for METLIFE Insurance company.

SOFTWARE

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

Vellore Institute of Technology - Vellore, Tamil Nadu

2010 to 2014

C.B.S.E.

Notre Dame Academy - Patna, Bihar

2007 to 2009

SKILLS

Java, Jsp, Html, Sql, C++, Javascript

 $\label{local_norm} $$ $$ https://www.indeed.com/r/Prakriti-Shaurya/5339383f9294887e? is id=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN $$$

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

- Good communication written and oral skills
- Excellent conceptual and analytical skills
- Effective interpersonal skills

PERSONALITY

- Communicative Punctuality
- Creativity Organized